[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The very advanced ocean liner, The Queen Mary II, was built in this country.", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Greece", "Liberia", "Ireland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why did Michael Corleone say he enlisted in the army?", "correct_answer": "Because of the attack on Pearl Harbor", "incorrect_answers": ["His brothers had enlisted", "To get out of the family business", "To learn how to kill"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Socrates had a successful service in this state institution in Athens.", "correct_answer": "Military", "incorrect_answers": ["Government", "Court", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a mixture of red and white sparkling wine, that has a high sugar content.", "correct_answer": "Cold Duck", "incorrect_answers": ["Barique", "Bodega", "Claret"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This movie released in 2004 has the following tag:  Whats the worst thing you ever did?  It stars Kevin Bacon and Kyra Sedgwick.", "correct_answer": "The Woodsman", "incorrect_answers": ["Tremors", "Where The Truth Lies", "Footloose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal translation of the word chatang, which refers toa traditional Chinese gruel sold as a snack on the street?", "correct_answer": "Tea soup", "incorrect_answers": ["Vegetable mash", "Dragon soup", "Flower tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "About how many feet are there in one kilometer?", "correct_answer": "3281", "incorrect_answers": ["1762", "5280", "2089"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Danny Archer at the end of the movie Blood Diamond?", "correct_answer": "He dies.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is flown to safety in a plane with Maddy Bowen.", "He sells the large blood diamond and shares the money with the village.", "He donates the proceeds of the diamond sale to the UN Commission dealing with conflict diamonds."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is diner-speak for an order of hash?", "correct_answer": "Customer will take a chance", "incorrect_answers": ["Burn the British", "Gravel train", "Pittsburgh"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She  was the first woman to wear high-heeled shoes.", "correct_answer": "Catherine DeMedici", "incorrect_answers": ["Cleopatra", "Joan of Arc", "Queen Elizabeth I"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which American Rock and Roller played a US Ranger in The Longest Day?", "correct_answer": "Fabian Forte", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby Rydell", "Frankie Valli", "James Darren"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From which law school did fictional character Elle Woods graduate?", "correct_answer": "Harvard", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanford", "Alabama", "Cambridge"]}]